♪ I, I LOVE THE COLORFUL
CLOTHES SHE WEARS ♪
♪ AND THE WAY THE SUNLIGHT
PLAYS UPON HER HAIR ♪
♪ I HEAR THE SOUND
OF A GENTLE WORD ♪
♪ ON THE WIND THAT LIFTS HER
PERFUME THROUGH THE AIR ♪
♪ I'M PICKIN' UP
GOOD VIBRATIONS ♪
♪ SHE'S GIVING ME
THE EXCITATIONS ♪
♪ I'M PICKIN' UP
GOOD VIBRATIONS ♪
♪ SHE'S GIVING ME
THE EXCITATIONS ♪
♪ GOOD, GOOD, GOOD,
GOOD VIBRATIONS ♪
♪ CLOSE MY EYES ♪
♪ SHE'S SOMEHOW CLOSER NOW ♪
♪ SOFTLY SMILE ♪
♪ I KNOW SHE MUST BE KIND ♪
♪ WHEN I LOOK IN HER EYES ♪
♪ SHE GOES WITH ME
TO A BLOSSOM WORLD ♪
♪ I'M PICKIN' UP
GOOD VIBRATIONS ♪
♪ SHE'S GIVING ME EXCITATIONS ♪
♪ I'M PICKIN' UP
GOOD VIBRATIONS ♪
♪ SHE'S GIVING ME EXCITATIONS ♪
♪ GOOD, GOOD, GOOD,
GOOD VIBRATIONS ♪
♪ EXCITATIONS ♪
♪♪♪
♪ AH ♪
♪ MY, MY, WHAT ELATION ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHERE ♪
♪ BUT SHE SENDS ME THERE ♪
♪ OH, MY, MY ♪
♪ WHAT A SENSATION ♪
♪ OH, MY, MY, WHAT ELATION ♪
♪ OH, MY, MY, WHAT ♪
(MUSIC SOFTENS)
♪ GOTTA KEEP THOSE
LOVIN' GOOD VIBRATIONS ♪
♪ A'HAPPENIN' WITH HER ♪
♪ GOTTA KEEP THOSE
LOVIN' GOOD VIBRATIONS ♪
♪ A'HAPPENIN' WITH HER ♪
♪ GOTTA KEEP THOSE LOVIN'
GOOD VIBRATIONS A-HAPPENIN' ♪
♪ AH ♪
♪ GOOD, GOOD, GOOD,
GOOD VIBRATIONS ♪
♪ NA, NA, NA, NA, NA ♪
♪ NA, NA, NA ♪
♪ DO, DO, DO, DO, DO ♪
♪ DO, DO, DO ♪
♪♪♪